Valentyna Tokarska

Front End Developer

I am a front-end developer with 1 year of experience in JavaScript, HTML and CSS. My professional experience also includes working with React.js and Angular frameworks. I am committed to providing exceptional customer service and active participation in the work environment. I like finding effective solutions and ensuring a high degree of customer satisfaction.

Portfolio: https://tokkaya79.github.io/portfolio-tokarskaya/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/valentina-

tokarskaya-708502252/

Github: https://github.com/tokkaya79

EXPERIENCE

CZ ImperialMedia

Front-end Developer

July 2022 - Present

- Web page styling according to the design/layout;
- Rewriting button logic;
- Introducing new components to existing projects;
- Refactoring written code;
- Bug fixes;
- Writing code that implements application logic;
- contact with designer;

KidsQest

Company owner

2016 - 2022

• Quest rooms for kids

Fitness club "Energy"

Coach

2015-2018

group fitness

Borol LTD

Chief Accountant

2000 - 2015

accounting and tax accounting wholesale trade and advertising services

CONTACTS

Wroclaw, Poland +48 730 699 868 tokkaya79@gmail.com

SKILLS

REACT
Angular,
JS(ES5,ES6)
TypeScript
PHP
MySQL,
WordPress
HTML5&CSS
SASS, SCSS,
Tailwind CSS
GIT
BEM

EDUCATION

European Financial University 2000 - 2004

Commercial Technical School 1996 - 1998

LANGUAGES

Polish B2 English B2 Ukrainian C3 Russian C3

RECOMMENDATIONS

CZ ImperialMedia Mikuláše Kolník +420 777 529 017